Cosplay Project Part 4
Yay!
It's done!
Are you okay?
Ta-da!
Next is...
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ahh...
Ernie likes peanuts.
He's cute.
It's the first time.
Ahaha.
After this video, I couldn't look at you.
You couldn't see me.
For the fourth video, I cosplayed as Mio Akiyama, a character named Mio Akiyama, in school uniform.
My name is Mio Akiyama, and I am playing a character named Mio Akiyama, and I am playing Mugi-chan.
I'm Mugi-chan. Kakki-chan is the one who thought of all the things to do this time. She thought of a lot of things.
It all started when Mayu called me in her memory, but I also had a dream.
I had a dream that I really wanted to have. I had a dream that I really wanted to do.
I have loved this K-ON! anime since I was in elementary school, and I thought I would definitely become Mio-chan when I became a high school student.
Is that so? That's right. I thought about joining the K-ON! club, but the instruments are too expensive.
Oh, that's true. I thought, "I don't have it because it's me. Because it's me.
So I couldn't join the K-ON! club, but now I'm here to make my dream come true.
Actually, there are five of us in the K-ON! That's right.
Who are the other three? Oh? Huh? That's not enough. Not enough.
That's what I thought. I can't do it.
I called the three of you. Come here.
Hello.
I called Rei-chan, Yuma, and Ayame.
Hello. First appearance.
Do you three know each other?
Yes, I did. I knew them. There's one person I don't know.
I don't watch anime at all, so this is my first time in the K-ON!
First of all, when I chose this person, it was my first decision.
I wanted Ayame to play Azunyan for sure. I had been thinking about it for a long time.
This was an instant decision.
Really?
I know. It looks really good on her right now.
It's so cute.
Super cute.
He's so cute. It's really like a real Azunyan.
Really? I'm glad.
And Yuna-chan.
And Yui.
Yui, you know, she's a little bit fluffy at times,
She's a very good guitarist and vocalist. She is the vocalist of this group.
I thought of her as a vocalist.
That was the connection.
Vocal connection.
And it's Yuna.
I thought you were a persimmon ego-player.
That's a little true.
That's true.
Thank you for having me.
And Rikchan, this is Rei-chan.
Hello.
I'm the only one with natural hair today.I'm the only one with natural hair today.
How do you like it?
It's perfect.
Really?
Kaki has been giving me a lot of love since this morning,
I've been grinning with happiness.
So, what do you want to do with the five of us here today?
I want to recreate the opening of K-ON with the five of us.
The opening is amazing.
The opening. It's great, isn't it?
It's something that can only be done with five people,
I thought it would be fun,
I thought it would be fun, but we don't have much time today.
Where are we? Really.
That's a lot of time.
Two hours in the car.
You have no idea what time it is in the morning.
I'm sorry.
But I don't have much time,
It's going to be a handmade reproduction music video,
I hope you will give me a warm welcome,
As much as possible.
I'll try to be careful before I go.
Let's go for it!
Which scene would you like to start with?
The scene in the armory.
From the scene where you play the instrument.
The school.
Go!
Amazing.
This is Hari-chan.
This angle of view is also Ririchan.
on the drums.
Amazing.
There's a guitar, too.
That's right.
First of all, I want to shoot this.
And the barley butt.
Wheat butt.
First of all, I need to set this up.
My guitar.
That's my forehead.
Rik-chan's forehead and my butt.
Where's the view?
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
All of you.
Butt first.
Okay.
Let's see here.
Is it heavy?
Yeah, it's heavy.
And I...
I'll just say it's facing this way.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God, I'm in the reflection.
Am I right?
Hey, turn around.
Am I facing the right way?
Yeah, just a little bit.
Let's do it this way.Let's do this.
Oh, this one's not connected.
Yes, yes, yes.
Let's do it this way.
Like this.
I'll only take it for a second.
Oh, yes.
One.
One. Two.
All right, two seconds should do it.
Okay, okay.
There you go.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
It's exactly like that.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
It looks good.
Just like this.
And now...
A scene with just Mugi-chan.
Oh, yeah!
Here we go.
I quit.
Are you being cute and cuddly? Are you okay?
Are you okay?
Cute and cuddly.
I'm coming in.
Okay, please.
Close the door a little.
What's with the color of the backdrop and everything?
The backdrop...
Uh...
That's it.
Close your eyes.
Okay, okay, okay.
Here we go.
Turn.
C8.
Here we go.
Ahhh...
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
I'm here 5, please... c 6, right?
I've got a camera angle of about chest-deep...
I'd like to see a little bit of the head, a little bit of the chest, a little bit of the head, a little bit of the chest, a little bit of the head, a little bit of the chest, a little bit of the head, a little bit of the head...
It's a little bit like a shop... a little bit like a shop... a little bit like a shop... a little bit like a shop...
I'm not that sleepy... but I'm really going to go to the top... from Fagler Way... and then to the 6th place!
Start the ballot...
Yeah!
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
That's good, isn't it?
That's a good idea
I smiled, didn't I? Here's a confirmation cut.
6 what an idiot.
OK!
Nice pace, nice pace.
What's next?
What's the next number?
59, I think.
C42, take two.
Oh, good, good, good, good. I like it, I like it, I like it.Oh, good, good, good. It's good, it's good, it's good.
It's good, right? It's good, isn't it?
I'm so happy. It's Mio's bass guitar.
It's amazing. Don't hug me.
Who's next?
Isn't that Yui?
Yui?
Oh, that's Yui's guitar.
Where is it?
Yui, this is the hardest part.
And it's the hardest part.
What?
While singing.
Don't wait until the end time.
Until the end time.
Fourteen C's.
Nice.
Please.
Yes, sir.
Ready!
I'll wait until the assembly chime.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Let's take a look. Let's see.
Let's see.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm not very good at this.
What do you think?
I think you're looking at the guitar.
Yeah, I think so.
And I'm on top of it, so I'm on the bottom.
Yes, yes, yes!
That's all I have to say.
C14!
Here we go.
All right, here we go!
Ready!
I'll wait until the assembly time.
Knock-knock.
You have a sense of rhythm, don't you?
Why do you suddenly lose your sense of rhythm?
Try rhythm.
Come on!
Yes, yes, yes!
Oh, now that's good!
Look here, look here, look here.
OK OK OK.
Shin-no-teen!
Yes!
Please.
Yo, ho!
Good, good, good, good, good!
Very good! Very good!
So good, so good, so good!
Next time, it's all of us.
At last!
All together?
Can I see the reference video?
Sure, sure.OK, OK.
It's OK.
I'm sorry, but I'm not sure I can do this.
Never-E,.
Never Ending Girl Talk
Jumping Dowl.
Mari might be a little more this way.
Yui is a little ahead.
Oh, really.
Yui's a little further in?
In front?
Too far?
Like this?
Sheena 13!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I want to do it.
I pulled this one again.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
This way.
Like this.
Ready?
I love it.
So cute!
It's really cute.
I wish I could take a picture with this.
Looks like something cosplayers would like.
Turn around.
So cute.
Like this, you can't take it because it's not on when you press it.
Okay, okay.
That means, if I don't turn it on, it won't open here.
I'm gonna have to waste one of these.
Oh, okay.
Okay, well, let's all, you know, let's all take a picture of this.
We're going to take one.
Oh, sure.
Okay, I'll take one... I'll take one.
I'm scared.
Oh, that's good, right?
Oh, you think you can get it?
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
Oh, yeah, that's good, right?
It's good, right?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Sorry about this.
You've been after persimmons from the start.
Kaki, pull it this way.
I was being pulled over here.
It's being pulled this way.
That's right.
That's tough.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I thought it was your right hand.
I started relatively early.
I'll start with my seniors.
Can I throw from the front?
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, please.Please.
I'll go.
Yes, sir.
Don't wait for me, the Czechs are coming.
Here it comes... here it comes...
Run, run, run.
Aah!
What do you think?
Oh, it's good, right?
Oh, because of the angle of view.
A little more front.
How about...?
Front.
Maybe the front.
This way? If I said "this way"...
Certainly.
Here we go.
Come on, please.
What do you think?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh, my God, I'm such an idiot. I didn't turn it.
One more time, one more time, one more time.
Again, again, again.
OK, I turned it.
Okay, I'll flush it.
Okay.
How's it look?
What do you think?
Oh, sorry.
You're so cute!
You've got twintails.
Oh, hey, are you worried?
Oh, you're so anxious.
It's from a cartoon.
I've got the letters.
What? Write it down!
Where do you read it?
Downstairs.
Oh, this...
I think you can do it.
That's good.
Shake it twice.
Too much fun.
Seino.
You idiot!
I want to do my hair more like this.
I want to make it look more like a cartoon.
I know...
I'm going to be an idiot!
Anytime!
Seino
Idiot!
Idiots!
What the hell?
If you'll excuse me for a moment...
I'm sorry...
You're so cute!That's so cute.
Oh, I like it.
Thank you.
It's alive. It's alive as a result.
Cute.
Okay, it's perfect. It's perfect.
Nice?
Oh, yeah.
One more time, please.
Oh, my God.
This one?
That'll work?
That's good.
Elizabeth.
What?
She's so cute!
I thought I wanted to do a constant issue now.
I didn't have the day.
There's some kind of sofa.
Oh, it's like a yui, a real one.
Hey, hey, hey
Oh, this is cute.
This is cute.
It's cute.
Cute!
A-ha-ha-ha
Cute.
Suddenly
Cute
Ha-ha-ha
I'm watching it with the others.
Heh heh heh
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Mystery dance
You're slipping.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
There's a very playful Miho. Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I didn't know she was this goofy.
[ED]
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's good, isn't it?
It's cute.
This one's okay.
Hello. - Hello.
I've finished shooting the video.
Today is another day.
I'd like to invite you to come with me.
Today we're going to shoot a song.
I'd like to shoot a song today.
Let's go for it!
I'll do my best!
Char.
It starts with char. The best char.Because it starts with char. The best char.
Let's serve the best char.
Okay, please.
Please.
[ED]
Thank you for the chakinagashi dekashimashita denpai.
I'm not waiting until the working chime.
Late but relative no no no
Italia futask as much as I can
Dokidoki ga nai stop no fuurustotoru na nao
hope and desire ribbon on the air
bring your own stories and snacks, new time version typing
I'm in a diary of love
I'll fly if I stuff my skirt only two centimeters
farther than yesterday, an octave higher than the day before
Japi na gachi gachi jyunshi nepper edicasong
Every day is a real live and it's brand new
I wake up early and go to bed early non non non
Shanti wasshoi all the way, shanti wasshoi all the way
Guti de fabulous nepper eddicus song
Frozen and aching mooning is a good thing to have
also memories are crushed in a ball
Futa e shania tak, shania tak
300ár
So it is completed.
Yay!
We finished shooting the song.
We've finished shooting the song.
And, you know, Kakki has a picture, too. Kakki's picture.
He draws pictures in places that seem to be difficult to draw these days.
Actually, he made masks.
Ah, masks.
I wonder how this is going to turn out.
Well, we are going to see the finished product for the first time,
Let's take a look.
Okay, everyone, let's put them on.
I'm so excited.
Wow!
That's amazing.
I drew the logo too.
Really?
Yes, I did.
You were so good.
You drew this too?
Yes, I also drew these around the logo.
What? Cute!
I thought you'd like it.
Oh, this one?
Yes, this one.
It's so awesome!
Keep it down! Keep going!
That's amazing!
That's so scary!
I totally didn't think about it!
It's pretty funny just the way it is!
It's funny as it is! I just wanted to move it a little bit.
I just wanted to move it a little bit, but there wasn't enough room to run, so it had to die just the way it was.
I worked so hard on it.
Red! Red!
Super cute!Super cute!
Cute! Cute!
Fill in the sideburns, fill in the sideburns, and the width of the bangs so much.
Then 0.5 would be fine.
0.7
I feel like I can do one shot ok.
Supervisor, please.
I'll change the mark.
Why did you come this way?
I thought it was this way.
Let's see the finished VTR.
Go ahead.
Thank you for watching.
Chaki na gachi shikashimashita nempaerigato
I don't wait until the work chime.
Relative no-no for tardiness
stadia afterschool as much as I can
Dokidoki ga nai nai full throttle na no nai
hope desire ribbon on the air
bring in a lot of material, hit the nu-tine version
men are forbidden to pre-chop, this guy was a cheater, nikki chop
If you only stuff your skirt two centimeters, it'll fly
farther than yesterday, an octave higher than the day before
Yippee, gutsy, loud, nepper-eddie-cast
Every day is a real live show, and it's brand new
I wake up early and go to bed early no no no no
Full of shanty-washon
Yippee, stiff and wonderful, Napper Edicast
Here's where the painful moaning comes in
And memories are abused again, gyui-go
Utarella shania tack
Please subscribe to our channel and rate us highly!